youthnoise.com 2016-12-03

# Privacy Policy - Digital Marketing Agency | Youth Noise | SEO Company

**Privacy Policy**

Welcome to the Youth Noise web site. This statement provides Youth Noise’s privacy policy on information that is collected through this web site and the use of that information.

 **In General**

Youth Noise may use the information it collects for management and promotion of Youth Noise. We will not sell or disclose your information for any other purpose without your written consent, unless there is a legal requirement for such disclosure. To the extent that Youth Noise discloses information to third-party contractors, those third parties will be required to follow this privacy policy.

 **Information Collected During Your Visit To This Web Site**

Youth Noise is the sole owner of the information collected on this site, [www.youthnoise.com](http://www.youthnoise.com/). Youth Noise collects information from its customers at several different points on our web site. By using our services and accessing our site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this statement, as modified from time to time by us. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post a new statement on our site and change the date indicated at the bottom of the statement. Therefore, we encourage you to check the date of our privacy policy statement whenever you visit this site for any updates or changes. Please see our Terms & Conditions under the Terms & Conditions link for a more detailed legal explanation of our general online policies.

 **Personal Information**

We collect several different types of information on our site. We collect “personal information,” which is information that can be used to identify you individually, such as your name, address and telephone number. Youth Noise employees may have access to your personal information only for legitimate business purposes, and are required to protect the confidentiality of your personal information.

 **Technical Information**

We automatically collect and store “technical information” about your visit to our site such as: (1) the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet; (2) the type of browser software and operating system used to access our site; (3) the date and time you access our site; and (4) the pages you visit on our site. The technical information collected will not personally identify you.

The following information explains in more detail the different forms of personal and technical information and how we may collect and use that information.

 **Order Forms**

We collect personal information in connection with the purchase of items sold from this site. We request information from the customer on order forms for all products sold. A customer must provide contact information (such as name, e-mail, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number and expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill orders. If we have trouble processing an order, the information may be used to contact the customer.

 **E-mail Address**

If you send us an e-mail with questions or comments or if you provide your e-mail address when ordering Youth Noise content and/or merchandise, Youth Noise may use your e-mail address and other personal information included in your correspondence to improve the content of our web site or to respond to your correspondence.

 **Children’s Privacy**

Youth Noise does not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from children through Youth Noise online order forms. If at any time Youth Noise learns that a child under the age of 13 has submitted personal information online, it will take all reasonable measures necessary to remove such information from its databases and not use such information for any purpose except where necessary to protect the safety of the child or others or as required by law.

 **Cookies**

A “cookie” is a small text file that a web site can place on your computer’s hard drive in order, for example, to collect technical information about your activities on the site or to make it possible for you to use an online “shopping cart” to keep track of items you wish to purchase. The “cookie” transmits this information back to the web site’s computer that, generally speaking, is the only computer that can read it. You may set your web browser to warn you whenever a site attempts to place a cookie on your computer or refuse to accept cookies. Youth Noise will use cookies collected during your visit to this site for the purpose of facilitating your use of our site and for maintaining statistics concerning use of our site that will help us make improvements. Technical information collected by cookies will not be linked to your personal information.

 **Notification of Changes**

Youth Noise reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy and will display any changes to this privacy policy to this web site 30 days before the changes become effective. If we decide to change this privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy policy statement, the homepage, and other pages we deem appropriate so our customers are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

 **How to Contact Us?**

If you have any questions about our privacy policy statement or our use of your information you can [contact us](http://www.youthnoise.com/contact/) directly.

 **Special Notice**

Effective Date of Privacy Policy: January 1, 2015

Use of this site signifies your acceptance of Youth Noise Web Site Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy.
